{
    "experiments": [
        { 
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "phrase",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is acceptor atoms?",
            "answer": "Trivalent atoms"
        },
        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "phrase",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is band-pass filter?",
            "answer": "A tuned circuit"
        },
        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "phrase",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is base biasing?",
            "answer": "A method of biasing a BJT"
        },


        { 
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE", 
            "granularity": "paragraph",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is bistable multivibrator?",
            "answer": "A multi vibrator with two stable states. An external signal is required to change the output from one state to the other. Also called a latch."
        },
        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "paragraph",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is audio?",
            "answer": "Relating to frequencies that can be heard by the human ear. Approximately 20 Hz to 20 kHz."
        },
        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "paragraph",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is band-pass filter?",
            "answer": "A tuned circuit designed to pass a band of frequencies between a lower cut-off frequency (f1) and a higher cut-off frequency (f2). Frequencies above and below the pass band are heavily attenuated."
        },


        { 
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE", 
            "granularity": "sentence",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is AC power supply?",
            "answer": "Power supply that delivers an AC voltage."
        },
        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "sentence",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is bandwidth?",
            "answer": "Width of the band of frequencies between the half power points."
        },
        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "sentence",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is average value?",
            "answer": "A value of voltage or current where the area of the wave above the value equals the area of the wave below the value."
        },




        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "phrase",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is acceptor atoms?",
            "answer": "Trivalent atoms"
        },
        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "phrase",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is band-pass filter?",
            "answer": "A tuned circuit"
        },
        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "phrase",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is base biasing?",
            "answer": "A method of biasing a BJT"
        },


        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "paragraph",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is bistable multivibrator?",
            "answer": "A multi vibrator with two stable states. An external signal is required to change the output from one state to the other. Also called a latch."
        },
        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "paragraph",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is audio?",
            "answer": "Relating to frequencies that can be heard by the human ear. Approximately 20 Hz to 20 kHz."
        },
        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "paragraph",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is band-pass filter?",
            "answer": "A tuned circuit designed to pass a band of frequencies between a lower cut-off frequency (f1) and a higher cut-off frequency (f2). Frequencies above and below the pass band are heavily attenuated."
        },


        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "sentence",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is AC power supply?",
            "answer": "Power supply that delivers an AC voltage."
        },
        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "sentence",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is bandwidth?",
            "answer": "Width of the band of frequencies between the half power points."
        },
        {
            "technique": "AUTOCOMPASTE",
            "granularity": "sentence",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is average value?",
            "answer": "A value of voltage or current where the area of the wave above the value equals the area of the wave below the value."
        },




        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "phrase",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is acceptor atoms?",
            "answer": "Trivalent atoms"
        },
        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "phrase",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is band-pass filter?",
            "answer": "A tuned circuit"
        },
        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "phrase",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is base biasing?",
            "answer": "A method of biasing a BJT"
        },


        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "paragraph",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is bistable multivibrator?",
            "answer": "A multi vibrator with two stable states. An external signal is required to change the output from one state to the other. Also called a latch."
        },
        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "paragraph",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is audio?",
            "answer": "Relating to frequencies that can be heard by the human ear. Approximately 20 Hz to 20 kHz."
        },
        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "paragraph",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is band-pass filter?",
            "answer": "A tuned circuit designed to pass a band of frequencies between a lower cut-off frequency (f1) and a higher cut-off frequency (f2). Frequencies above and below the pass band are heavily attenuated."
        },


        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "sentence",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is AC power supply?",
            "answer": "Power supply that delivers an AC voltage."
        },
        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "sentence",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is bandwidth?",
            "answer": "Width of the band of frequencies between the half power points."
        },
        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "sentence",
            "knowledge": "known",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is average value?",
            "answer": "A value of voltage or current where the area of the wave above the value equals the area of the wave below the value."
        },




        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "phrase",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is acceptor atoms?",
            "answer": "Trivalent atoms"
        },
        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "phrase",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is band-pass filter?",
            "answer": "A tuned circuit"
        },
        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "phrase",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is base biasing?",
            "answer": "A method of biasing a BJT"
        },


        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "paragraph",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is bistable multivibrator?",
            "answer": "A multi vibrator with two stable states. An external signal is required to change the output from one state to the other. Also called a latch."
        },
        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "paragraph",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is audio?",
            "answer": "Relating to frequencies that can be heard by the human ear. Approximately 20 Hz to 20 kHz."
        },
        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "paragraph",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is band-pass filter?",
            "answer": "A tuned circuit designed to pass a band of frequencies between a lower cut-off frequency (f1) and a higher cut-off frequency (f2). Frequencies above and below the pass band are heavily attenuated."
        },


        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "sentence",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is AC power supply?",
            "answer": "Power supply that delivers an AC voltage."
        },
        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "sentence",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is bandwidth?",
            "answer": "Width of the band of frequencies between the half power points."
        },
        {
            "technique": "TRADITIONAL",
            "granularity": "sentence",
            "knowledge": "unknown",
            "data_file": "data/texts.json",
            "question": "What is average value?",
            "answer": "A value of voltage or current where the area of the wave above the value equals the area of the wave below the value."
        }
    ]
}
